{
    "id": "6f8586141ec449b69fcd1fce3bdae5d8",
    "title": "Many And Many Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………… families own more than one vehicle these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b16ed391dd93487cae0f44474ee64d60"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... us are disappointed with the government’s economic policies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "545491b223964f308c8b9bd47dfee6d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. them are late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "066338001d82496f8c7774fb240974a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "There weren’t ………………… students in the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f4462659e304f3da69e00d1464f3316"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ..................... you have submitted your assignments?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9054f21042af4ce4b9c98ce244240b4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got ……………….. friends in the city.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ff8d94fa9e9a4a2681ba97a0bad4ef10"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… them are not interested in the offer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3fa431e04d304f348261d6162e5c712e"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t ………………… apples on the tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5c9bdb17504b4845be4cf3bd3ca9357c"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………… people were there?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9975b482a30a41138df8736858f3de4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… those who participated in the program said that they enjoyed it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24db7a0516ff43978a4af785e0b278b2"
        }
    ]
}